<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Response>
  	<Start>
      <Transcription statusCallbackUrl="https://22c9-147-161-170-176.ngrok-free.app/sport" speechModel="telephony" transcriptionEngine="google"  hints='goal, offsite, corner kick, yellow card, red card, owngoal, foul' track="outbound_track"/> 
    </Start>    
    <Say language="en-GB" voice="Polly.Arthur-Neural">The live commentary is starting now!</Say>
    <Pause length="1"/>
  	<Say language="en-GB" voice="Polly.Arthur-Neural">And we’re underway at Anfield! Liverpool in their famous red, Manchester United in white—two historic rivals, and you can feel the tension already!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>United start with early possession, calmly working it around the back—Maguire finds Dalot on the right, looking for an option.<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>Here come Liverpool! Mac Allister into Salah, cutting inside—lovely footwork—he threads it through to Núñez—OH, but Varane gets a toe in at the last second!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>United push forward now—Fernandes dropping deep, spraying a pinpoint diagonal to Rashford—one-on-one with Alexander-Arnold—early cross—Van Dijk heads clear!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>McTominay wins it in midfield, feeds Højlund—he turns! He’s going for goal from distance—Ohhh, just wide! That had Alisson scrambling!<break strength="x-weak" time="400ms"/>Liverpool piling on the pressure now—Szoboszlai spreads it wide to Robertson, who whips it in—Núñez gets up! Header! OH, what a save from Onana! He keeps United level!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>United counter quickly—Fernandes slides it to Rashford—he’s got the pace—skips past Konaté—into the box! Shoots! BLOCKED by Van Dijk! Outstanding defending!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>Yellow card! Oh, and the referee’s had enough there! Casemiro comes in late on Mac Allister, catching him on the ankle—he’s into the book, and no complaints from the United man.<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>Corner for Liverpool—Robertson delivers—Van Dijk climbs! Powerful header—IT'S IN! GOAL FOR LIVERPOOL! The captain delivers, and Anfield erupts! Liverpool 1, Manchester United 0!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>United looking for a quick response—McTominay finds Fernandes, who tries to slip it through to Højlund—but Van Dijk is there again! He’s been a rock at the back so far.<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>Liverpool are relentless—Alexander-Arnold darts forward, links up with Salah—beautiful give-and-go—Salah into the box! Drills it low—Oh, Núñez is inches away from tapping it in!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>United trying to control the tempo now—Casemiro spreading it wide to Dalot, looking for Rashford—he gets past his man! Cross comes in—Højlund with a header—straight at Alisson!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>Liverpool break again! Szoboszlai drives forward, slides it to Gakpo—he cuts inside, goes for goal—OH, JUST OVER THE BAR! Anfield thought that was in!<break strength="medium" time="400ms"/>It’s been an electrifying opening twenty minutes—Liverpool leading through Van Dijk’s header, but United still in it. This one is shaping up to be an absolute classic!</Say>
    <Pause length="10"/>
    <Say>End!</Say>
</Response>
